let questions = [
    {
        question: "What does HTML mainly do?",
        options: [ "Styles a page", "Add dynamic functionality to pages", "Displays a page"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What does CSS mainly do?",
        options: [ "Styles a page", "Add dynamic functionality to pages", "Displays a page"],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What does JavaScript mainly do?",
        options: [ "Styles a page", "Add dynamic functionality to pages", "Displays a page"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which HTML element is not normally used?",
        options: [ "<section>", "<br>", "<html>", "<part>"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which JavaScript keyword is not real?",
        options: [ "function", "of", "valueof", "return"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which CSS style attribute is correct?",
        options: [ "font-width", "font-family", "border-length", "border-circumference"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Where in html code do you normally store the title?",
        options: [ "<header>", "<body>", "<section>", "<head>"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which selects an element inside of another element",
        options: [ ".scoreboard span", "button, h1", ".inside", ".scoreboard.hidden"],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Which calls a function in JavaScript?",
        options: [ "store();", "increment = 2;", "console.log;", "{ a:1, b:2 };"],
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "Which symbol is used to select the id of an element on the page",
        options: [ "*", "#", ".", "+"],
        answer: 1
    }
]